Sunil Kumar Chauhan (1) Featured

Associate Manager seeking roles in Qlikview, Qliksense, Nprinting, Power Bi, Tableau Software Development, Requirement Analysis, Business Intelligence, Stakeholder Management, Delivery Management, Team Management



Current Designation: Associate Manager Total Experience: 14 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Notice Period: 2 Months Current Company: Virtusa Consulting Services Pvt. Ltd.

Current Location: Gurgaon Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Gurgaon, Noida, Delhi / NCR

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Associate Manager, Team Lead/Tech Lead, Development, Requirement Gathering, Requirement Analysis, Business Intelligence, Stakeholder Management, Delivery Management, Team Management, Agile

Methodology, Knowledge Transfer

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Competent Professional with over 14 years of experience in leading Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC) right from requirement analysis, documentation, coding and testing (preparation of test cases along with implementation) to maintenance of proposed applications

Designed solutions that employed modern ML & BI techniques; delivered solutions that are highly performant and lead to a higher degree of automation

Developed web application solutions by studying information needs, conferring with users, studying systems flow, usage and

Presented BI technology vision, roadmaps &blue prints and project plans.

Expertise in designing, implementing & maintaining Web based Qlikview BI Applications, Qlikview Server, QMC, Creating jobs, license allocation (CAL)

Work Experience

Virtusa Consulting Services Pvt. Ltd. as Associate Manager Feb 2020 to Till Date

Qlikview,Qliksense,Nprinting,OrientDB,Gremlin,SQL server

Polaris Consulting and Services Ltd. as Team Leader Nov 2012 to Feb 2020

Qlikview, Qliksense, nprinting, GraphDb,OrientDB,gremlin query

Netlink Software Pvt. Ltd as Sr. Qlikview Developer Jan 2011 to Nov 2012

Team Computers Pvt. Ltd as Software Developer Mar 2010 to Jan 2011

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from NIIST institute in 2005

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

ML

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Tensor Flow, ScikitLearn			
Oracle 11 ,SQL Server			
Windows XP, Windows 2007/2008			
Qlikview Web server, IIS			
Qlik Sense	november20	2020	2 Year(s) 4 Month(s)
Nprinting	18	2020	4 Year(s) 1 Month(s)

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

US Work Status: Need H1 Visa

Job Type: Permanent / Temporary

Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time